So over the last lectures, we moved all the asynchronous code and I can remove the axios import from
Bu yzden son derslerde, tm asenkron kodlar tadk ve eksenlerin ie aktarlmasn sipari
the order action creator file.
eylemi yaratcs dosyasndan kaldrabiliriz.
So we moved all the asynchronous code and even the synchronous side effect code from our action creator
Bu nedenle, senkronize olmayan tm kodlar ve hatta senkronize edilmi yan efekt
files to our sagas.
kodunu eylem yaratcmzdaki dosyalarmzdan somalarmza tadk.
The advantage in quotation marks because it's not necessarily better,
Trnak iaretlerindeki avantaj, nk mutlaka daha iyi deil, tercih
it depends on what you prefer.
ettiiniz eye baldr.
So the advantage can be that our action creators are all very lean,
Bu nedenle, avantajmz, eylem ierik oluturucularmzn ok yaln olabileceidir,
they really do just one thing,
gerekten sadece bir
they create an action
ey yaparlar, baka
they don't run any other code and all our side effect code, so the code that is not related to reduces
bir kod altrmadklar bir eylem olutururlar ve tm yan etki kodlarmz, dolaysyla ilgili olmayan
or to actions is in our sagas.
kodlar azalr veya eylemler bizim sagasmzda.
This is where we have our API calls, our local storage calls where we even might change the route
Bulunduumuz rotay bile deitirebileceimiz API arlarmz, yerel
we're currently on.
depolama arlarmz.
This is a pattern you don't have to use but it leads to leaner action creators.
Bu, kullanmak zorunda kalmayacanz bir desendir, ancak daha az hareketli aksiyon oluturuculara yol aar.
Now there are a couple of other things I want to show you with redux saga which you also should be aware of
imdi size, farknda olmanz gereken ve gerekten gl uygulamalar oluturmanza izin vermeniz gereken redux destan
and which should allow you to build really powerful applications.
ile size gstermek istediim birka ey daha var.